export const quiz = {
  question_1: {
    question:
      "Which Southeast Asian country is famous for its stunning beaches and islands like Bali and Komodo Island?",
    answer: "Indonesia",
  },
  question_2: {
    question:
      "Which North Asian country is famous for its iconic landmark, Red Square and the historic Kremlin?",
    answer: "Russia",
  },
  question_3: {
    question:
      "Which Western European country is famous for its stunning scenery, including the Scottish Highlands and Loch Ness?",
    answer: "Ireland",
  },
  question_4: {
    question:
      "Which Western European country is famous for its tulip fields, windmills and wooden shoes?",
    answer: "Netherlands",
  },
  question_5: {
    question:
      "Which European country was the birthplace of the Renaissance, with influential figures such as Leonardo da Vinci and Michelangelo?",
    answer: "Italy",
  },
  question_6: {
    question:
      "Which European country is known for its banking sector and the headquarters of many international financial institutions? ",
    answer: "Switzerland",
  },
  question_7: {
    question:
      "Which European country is famous for its chocolate industry and produces some of the best chocolates in the world?",
    answer: "Belgium",
  },
  question_8: {
    question:
      "Which African country is home to the Sahara Desert, the largest hot desert in the world?",
    answer: "Algeria",
  },
  question_9: {
    question: "Which country is the largest by area in America?",
    answer: "Canada",
  },
  question_10: {
    question: "Which country is the birthplace of tango dance?",
    answer: "Argentina",
  },
};
